# Anders G. Nordby



# Motzfeldtsgate 14, N-0187 Oslo, NORWAY (+47) 932 20 333 anders@delichon.no https://www.linkedin.com/in/agnordby/

#### DESCRIPTION

Anders is a project manager, systems architect and senior developer with customer focus and many years of experience in the industry. He holds the **PRINCE2 Practitioner**, **PRINCE2 Foundation** and **Certified Scrum Master** certifications, and he has also had the role of *team leader* and *scrum master* in several projects.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

05.2019 - PRESENT

#### Delichon AS

## Systems Architect & Senior Developer

Roles: Daily Manager and currently the only employee.

Customers: Element Logic, ABB.

**Technologies:** Azure DevOps, Azure DB, Azure WebServices, Akka.NET, TypeScript, React JS, C#, Microsoft .NET Core 2.2, Microsoft .NET Standard, ASP.NET Core MVC, ASP.NET, Keycloak, TFS, Octopus Deploy, Git, Powershell.

01.2018 - 04.2019

#### Sopra Steria

# Lead Software Engineer

**Roles:** In-house architect responsible for planning and QA of offers to customers. Senior developer for some customers.

Customers: Skatteetaten, Helsedirektoratet.

**Technologies:** C#, .Net, Episerver CMS, ASP.NET MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, JavaScript, Jira, Confluence, TFS, Git.

03.2014 - 08.2017

### CGI

#### Senior Web Developer

**Roles:** Team-leder, scrum master, hands-on architect.

**Customers:** ASKO, Fellesforbundet, Tekna, PIA, Miljødirektoratet. **Technologies:** C#, inRiver PIM, Apptus eSales, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, IdentityServer, T-SQL, NServiceBus, Jira, Confluence, jMeter, BlazeMeter, Angular.js, Knockout.js.

03.2010 - 02.2014

# Making Waves / Tarantell Senior Systems Consultant

Roles: Senior developer and team leader in several customer projects. Customers: The Norwegian Government, Arcus, The Norwegian Board of Health Administration, Canal Digital Kabel, Synoptik, NMD. Technologies: C#, .Net, NewRelic, PowerShell, jQuery, PowerShell, Jira, Confluence, TFS, SubVersion

08.2008 – 12.2009	Creuna, Consultant / Systems Developer
02.2006 - 07.2008	Ocelluz, Systems Developer & Project Manager
10.2004 - 02.2008	Anders Nordby Konsulenttjenester
05.1995 - 06.2002	Ajilon, Consultant

# KEY COMPETENCIES

Processes

Systemarkitektur, Scrum, Kanban, prosjektledelse.

Development

Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, Episerver Find, C#, ASP.Net, MVC, Apptus eSales, inRiver PIM, IdentityServer, T-SQL, PL/SQL, JavaScript, JSON, Ajax, NServiceBus, WCF, WebServices, REST, WebAPI, XML, HTML, CSS, jQuery, PowerShell, LATEX.

Tools

Jira, Confluence, Git, TFS, SubVersion, ReSharper, NewRelic, jMeter, BlazeMeter, NuGet.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

202I	Certified Optimizely Developer
2020	Microsoft Azure Fundamentals
2019	PRINCE2 Practitioner
2019	Certified Scrum Master
2018	PRINCE2 Foundation
2016	Certified inRiver Developer

#### **COURSES**

:	2019	Iom Gilb: Architecture Workshop
:	2018	Sopra Steria: Arkitekturskolen
	2015	Microsoft: Lead Enterprise Architect Programme

#### **EDUCATION**

0.11

4 1 ..

2003 – 2004	University of Oslo, Teacher Training
1999 – 2000	Oslo Business Academy, IT Candidate
1987 – 1996	University of Oslo, Cand.Mag.
1984 – 1987	Eikeli High School, Natural Sciences

#### **AWARDS**

2013-2017 Episerver Most Valued Professional

#### LANGUAGES

EXCELLENT	Norwegian (native), English
INTERMEDIATE	Bulgarian
BEGINNER	Spanish, German, Japanese